{
    "subject": "resource/The_Towering_Inferno",
    "predicate": "property/starring",
    "object": "resource/Susan_Blakely",
    "human_readable": "Susan Blakely stars in The Towering Inferno.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.7906407117843628,
            "question": "Who stars in the movie 'The Towering Inferno'?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.777606189250946,
            "question": "Name an actress who appeared in 'The Towering Inferno'."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6965911984443665,
            "question": "Who played a role in the film 'The Towering Inferno'"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5833091735839844,
            "question": "In what film does Susan Blakely appear?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5753668546676636,
            "question": "What is the name of the movie starring Susan Blakely?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5305062532424927,
            "question": "Susan Blakely is known for her role in which type of movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31040817499160767,
            "question": "What genre does 'The Towering Inferno' belong to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.02176184579730034,
            "question": "Can you name a famous disaster movie?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.018720243126153946,
            "question": "Which film involves a fire?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.01694859005510807,
            "question": "What movie features a disaster scenario?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Susan Blakely stars in The Towering Inferno.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4108_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Which film involves a fire?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4108_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name a famous disaster movie?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4108_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre does 'The Towering Inferno' belong to?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4108_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_109.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_124.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_63.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4108_92.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Susan Blakely stars in The Towering Inferno\" according to the provided documents:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nReasoning:\nThe documents provide several instances where Susan Blakely's involvement with The Towering Inferno is mentioned. Specifically, it mentions that she was a part of the impressive supporting cast for The Towering Inferno (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4108/re-ranker-msmarco/9.txt), and that her films include Towering Inferno (starring Paul Newman, Steve McQueen and other greats) as mentioned in file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_4108/re-ranker-msmarco/12.txt. This information collectively supports the triple that Susan Blakely stars in The Towering Inferno."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents mention that Susan Blakely starred in the film \"The Towering Inferno\" (1974), which supports the statement that Susan Blakely stars in The Towering Inferno."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}